ABDALLAH MOHAMED

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



+0201204484436



abduallah.mohamed.am@gmail.com



Elmasaken Eleqtsadya block 50 -Helwan - Cairo

PRO SKILLS



PERSONAL SKILLS



PERSONAL SKILLS

OBJECTIVE

To have an outstanding work opportunity in an organization where I can have the best use of my skills and my experience as well, employ my potentials to achieve excellent in my work, make a positive change in my job that can provide me a career development path.

JOB EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER AS A FREELANCER

SEP 2018 - PRESENT

Started my first job as a web developer where I had some small fullstack jobs which lead to bigger jobs:)

CASHIER AT ELMADINA ELMONOURA RESTRUANT

OCT 2016 - AUG 2018

A tempraroy job beside my colloge study to provide for my self

SALESMAN AT HAYAH CO.

MAY 2017 - JUN 2018

There's where I have learned about marketing and how to promote my self and my products

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE FROM AKHBAR ELYOM ACADEMY

SEP 2016 - JUN 2020

HOBBIES

